Guide to the Henry Leveke Kamphoefner Papers, 1924 - 1990 MC 00198
Special Collections Research Center
- Photographs and Postcards, 1.75 Linear feet; 3.5 archival boxes
  This series contains several thousand photographs of Kamphoefner's projects, friends, associates, and family, along with some photographs of buildings designed by other architects. All of Kamphoefner's built projects are represented, with the exception of the McEvare Residence in Southern Pines, North Carolina. The postcard collection contains images of chiefly European buildings, possibly collected during Kamphoefner's trip to Europe in 1930. Photographs are arranged first by size, then by subject. Note: This arrangement causes several subjects to be spread among separate containers.
  - Henry L. Kamphoefner Portraits, 1957-1985, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Pets, 1935, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Travels, 1961, 1964, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Family and Friends, 1960, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Student Drawings, 1932, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Grandview Music Pavilion
    - Sketches and Renderings, , [no date] (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Construction Prints, 1934, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Documentary Prints, 1934, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Fort Dodge Music Shell, 1938, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Music Shell for Olney, Illinois, Renderings, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Rural Resettlement Administration, Three-Bedroom House [1 item], [no date] (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - University of Oklahoma, Architecture Program, 1937-1938, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - University of Oklahoma, Schermerhorn Fellowship, Solar House, 1939, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Residence at Norman, Oklahoma
    - Mounted Prints by Cole Weston, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Interiors, 1947, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Exteriors, 1942, 1947, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Color Prints, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Edwards Mausoleum Plans and Rendering, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Residence at Raleigh, North Carolina
    - Prints by Andr Kertsz, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Proof Prints by Andr Kertsz, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Documentary Photographs, [no date] (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Henry L. Kamphoefner Passport Photographs, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Henry and Mabel Kamphoefner, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mabel Kamphoefner, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Trip to Mexico [File 1 of 2], circa 1979, 1983, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Trip to Mexico [File 2 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Family and Friends
    - [File 1 of 6], 1966-1973, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - [File 2 of 6], 1952, 1956, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - [File 3 of 6], 1965-1966, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - [File 4 of 6], 1937, 1953, 1972, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - [File 5 of 6], 1938-1939, 1953, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - [File 6 of 6], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Greetings, [no date], 1949, 1952, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Contact Prints, 1931, 1935-1936, 1966, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Cards Drawn by Henry Kamphoefner, 1931-1932 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Colleagues[File 1 of 2], 1936, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Colleagues [File 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Kamphoefner Student Drawings and Competition Entries [File 1 of 2], 1929-1932, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Kamphoefner Student Drawings and Competition Entries, [File 2 of 2], 1929, 1932, 1936, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, Sioux City, Iowa, c. 1935 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Crescent City Jewelry Company, Sioux City, Iowa, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Grandview Music Pavilion
    - Construction Photographs, 1934-1935, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Completed Project, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Details [File 1 of 2], 1934-1935, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Details [File 2 of 2], 1934-1935, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Music Shell, Fort Dodge, Iowa, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - University of Oklahoma
    - Campus Planning, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Faculty, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Visit by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Schermerhorn Fellowship Model, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Residence in Norman, Oklahoma
    - Architectural Model, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Construction Photographs, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Documentary Photographs, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - School of Design, Miscellaneous Student Project, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Buildings
    - Statues
      - [File 1 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - [File 2 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - [File 3 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - [File 4 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - [File 5 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Washington, D.C., [no date] (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Williamsburg, Virginia, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - University of Virginia, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Buildings by Frank Lloyd Wright
      - [File 1 of 3], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - [File 2 of 3], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - [File 3 of 3], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Bandshell Models
      - [no date] (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - Miscellaneous Bandshells
        - [File 1 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 47)
        - [File 2 of 5], 1933-1946, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 48)
        - [File 3 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 49)
        - [File 4 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 50)
        - [File 5 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 51)
      - Miscellaneous Buildings
        - [File 1 of 10], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 52)
        - [File 2 of 10], 1973, 1977, 1987, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 53)
        - [File 3 of 10], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 54)
        - [File 4 of 10], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 55)
        - [File 5 of 10], 1958, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 56)
        - [File 6 of 10], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 57)
        - [File 7 of 10], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 58)
        - [File 8 of 10], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 59)
        - [File 9 of 10], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 60)
        - [File 10 of 10], 1931, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 61)
        - Henry L. Kamphoefner, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Contact Prints, 1935-1936, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Negatives
    - Henry L. Kamphoefner
      - [File 1 of 6], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 63)
      - [File 2 of 6], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 64)
      - [File 3 of 6], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 65)
      - [File 4 of 6], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 66)
      - [File 5 of 6], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 67)
      - [File 6 of 6], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Family and Friends [File 1 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Family and Friends [File 2 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Family, Friends, and Colleagues [File 1 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Family, Friends, and Colleagues [File 2 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Miscellaneous Travels [File 1 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous Travels [File 2 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Christmas Card Drawings by Kamphoefner, 1931, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Student Drawings and Competition Entries
      - [File 1 of 4], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 76)
      - [File 2 of 4], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 77)
      - [File 3 of 4], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 78)
      - [File 4 of 4], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Student Drawings [See MC198.52-.53 for originals], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Crescent City Jewelry Company, Sioux City, Iowa, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Grandview Music Pavilion, Sioux City, Iowa, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Fort Dodge Music Shell, Fort Dodge, Iowa, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Colleagues (Oklahoma?), [no date] (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Residence in Norman, Oklahoma
      - Construction[File 1 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 85)
      - Construction [File 2 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 86)
      - Interior
        - [File 1 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 87)
        - [File 2 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 88)
        - [File 3 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 89)
        - [File 4 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 90)
        - [File 5 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 91)
        - [File 6 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 92)
        - [File 7 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 93)
        - [File 8 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 94)
        - [File 9 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 95)
        - [File 10 of 11], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 96)
        - [no date] [File 11 of 11] (Box 20, Folder 97)
      - Exterior
        - [File 1 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 98)
        - [File 2 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 99)
        - [File 3 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 100)
        - [File 4 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 101)
        - [File 5 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 102)
        - [File 6 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 103)
        - [File 7 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 104)
        - [File 8 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 105)
        - [File 9 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 106)
        - [File 10 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 107)
        - [File 11 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 108)
        - [File 12 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 109)
        - [File 13 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 110)
        - [File 14 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 111)
        - [File 15 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 112)
        - [File 16 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 113)
        - [File 17 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 114)
        - [File 18 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 115)
        - [File 19 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 116)
        - [File 20 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 117)
        - [File 21 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 118)
        - [File 22 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 119)
        - [File 23 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 120)
        - [File 24 of 24], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 121)
      - Architectural Model, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 122)
    - School of Design, Visit by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 123)
    - Miscellaneous Buildings
      - Williamsburg, Virginia, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 124)
      - Bandshells, [no date] (Box 20, Folder 125)
      - Taliesin West [File 1 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 126)
      - Taliesin West [File 2 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 127)
      - Buildings by Frank Lloyd Wright [File 1 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 128)
      - Buildings by Frank Lloyd Wright [File 2 of 2], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 129)
      - [File 1 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 130)
      - [File 2 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 131)
      - [File 3 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 132)
      - [File 4 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 133)
      - [File 5 of 5], [no date] (Box 20, Folder 134)
  - Postcard Collection, Miscellaneous European Buildings
  - Photographs
    - School of Design, Student Projects, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Projects, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Museum of Modern Art Exhibit, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Faculty and Students, 1983-1985, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Visit by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Photograph Album, Visits by Wright and Wijdeveld, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Photographs
    - Addition to Brooks Hall, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Buildings by Frank Lloyd Wright; Johnson Wax and Florida Southern College, 1950, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - By Philip Johnson, 1949-1970, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Bandshells, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Buildings, 1959-1976, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Artifacts and Memorabilia, 1924-1990, 1942-1965; 1.5 Linear feet; 3 archival boxes
  This series includes biographical sketches, personal finance information, wills, and purchases relating to residences in Norman, Oklahoma and Raleigh, North Carolina. The series also includes driver's licenses, membership cards, a diary from Kamphoefner's European trip in 1930, and several desktop items including his signature stamp. There also is a guest book from a memorial service held in Kamphoefner's honor after his death in 1990.
  - Biographical Sketches and Information, 1940-1982, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings and Articles, 1930-1985, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Caricatures, 1969, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Programs from Presentations to Kamphoefner, 1930-1980, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Grade Reports, 1924-1928 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Reprinted Poems, 1957, [no date] (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Wills and Estate Settlements, Kamphoefners, 1976-1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Wills and Estate Settlements, Extended Family, 1921-1965, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Papers, 1948-1980, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Insurance Policies, 1948-1987, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Financial Investments, Petro-Lewis, Inc., 1983-1986, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Residence in Norman, Invoices and Receipts, 1942-1948 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Residence in Norman, Lot Purchase and Specifications, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Residence in Raleigh
    - Draft Specifications, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Construction Invoices and Receipts, 1949-1979, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Furnishings Invoices and Receipts, 1949-1983, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Landscaping and Appraisals, 1950-1987, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Travel Information and Itineraries, 1961-1982, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Programs and Invitations, 1938-1985, [no date] (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Desktop Artifacts and Signature Stamp [8 items] (Box 24)
  - Driver's Licenses, 1907-1947, [no date] (Box 25)
  - Membership Cards, 1933-1947, 1972, [no date] (Box 25)
  - Bookplate, [no date] (Box 25)
  - Identification Label, Brass [1700 Map of Rome, Ignazio Benedetti, Gift of Henry and Mabel Kamphoefner], [no date] (Box 25)
  - Sketchbook, Sights in England, 1930 (Box 25)
  - Diary, European Travels, 1930 (Box 25)
  - Membership Keys, Phi Kappa Phi and Unidentified, [no date] (Box 25)
  - Guestbook, Kamphoefner Memorial Service, April 19, 1990 (Box 25)
- Oversized Materials, 1927-1952
  This series chiefly includes architectural drawings done by Kamphoefner throughout his career. It also includes several study drawings done by Kamphoefner as a student between 1927 and 1932. All of Kamphoefner's built projects are represented as well as several competition entries and proposed projects. There are several oversized photographs as well. There is also one folder of diplomas, awards, and certificates earned by Kamphoefner. A series of scrapbooks that were kept by Mabel Kamphoefner is found at the end of the series. The scrapbooks document Henry Kamphoefner's achievements throughout his career with special emphasis on the success of the School of Design at North Carolina State University. The series is arranged first by general size of the material, then by subject. Accordingly, several subjects are spread among folders.
  - Music Pavilion and Outdoor Theatre, Grandview Park, Sioux City, Iowa
    - Sketch of relief sculpture, charcoal on paper, mounted on press board [File 1 of 3], 1934 (Flatfolder 26)
    - Sketch of relief sculpture, charcoal on paper, mounted on press board [File 2 of 3], 1934 (Flatfolder 27)
    - Photograph, black and white [File 3 of 3], 1934 (Flatfolder 28)
  - Music Pavilion at Oleson Park, Fort Dodge, Iowa, 5 sheets, ink on paper, 1936 (Flatfolder 29)
  - Music Shell at Olathe, Kansas, Floor plans and elevations, pencil on tracing paper, 5 sheets, 1940 (Flatfolder 30)
  - Kamphoefner Residence in Norman, Oklahoma, Photograph, black and white, mounted on matte board, 1942 (Flatfolder 31)
  - University of Oklahoma Campus Planning, Photostats, 5 Sheets (Flatfolder 32)
  - Kamphoefner Residence in Raleigh, North Carolina
    - Floor plan, ink on press board [File 1 of 7], 1949 (Flatfolder 33)
    - Living area, photograph, black and white [File 2 of 7], 1949 (Flatfolder 34)
    - Living area, photograph, black and white [File 3 of 7], 1949 (Flatfolder 35)
    - South west elevation, photograph, black and white [File 4 of 7], 1949 (Flatfolder 36)
    - North east elevation, photograph, black and white [File 5 of 7], 1949 (Flatfolder 37)
    - North east elevation, photograph, black and white [File 6 of 7], 1949 (Flatfolder 38)
    - Dining area, photograph, black and white [File 7 of 7], 1949 (Flatfolder 39)
  - Mausoleum for Robert James Edwards, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma
    - Section, ink on press board [File 1 of 3], 1947 (Flatfolder 40)
    - Rendering watercolor on paper, matted [File 2 of 3], 1947 (Flatfolder 41)
    - Plan with landscape, ink on press board [File 3 of 3], 1947 (Flatfolder 42)
  - Diplomas, Awards, and Certificates [47 items], 1930-1986 (Flatfolder 43)
  - Court House Square, Olathe, Kansas, Plot Plan, Blueprint, 1939 (Flatfolder 44)
  - Music Pavilion and Outdoor Theatre, Grandview Park, Sioux City, Iowa, Working drawings, blueprints, 15 sheets, 1934
  - Sketches for Proposed Bandshell, Olathe, Kansas, 3 items, charcoal and ink on paper, Nat Baker, artist, 1940 (Flatfolder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Drawings and Blueprints
    - "A Music Shell for a Small Town," plan of the stage, [no date] (Flatfolder 46)
    - Proposed remodeling for the School of Architecture, University of Oklahoma (Flatfolder 46)
    - Design Schedule for Class "B" and "C", Spring Semester, 1945-1946 (Flatfolder 46)
    - Alternate kitchen layout for the L.O.F. House, Blueprint, [no date] (Flatfolder 46)
  - Kamphoefner Residence in Raleigh, North Carolina
    - Plan, ink on press board [File 1 of 4], 1949 (Flatfolder 47)
    - Perspective looking South, ink and watercolor on press board [File 2 of 4], 1949 (Flatfolder 48)
    - Perspective of living space toward dining-space, ink on press board [File 3 of 4], 1949 (Flatfolder 49)
    - Perspective looking North, ink and watercolor on press board [File 4 of 4], 1949 (Flatfolder 50)
  - Edwards Mausoleum, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, Renderings, ink and watercolor on press board, Nat Baker, artist, 1947 (Flatfolder 51)
  - Kamphoefner Student Drawings
    - Sketch of man standing, charcoal on paper, [no date] (Flatfolder 52)
    - "Thirteenth"-floor plan of elaborate building, charcoal and ink on paper, 1931 (Flatfolder 52)
    - "Analytique" historic composition, ink and watercolor on paper, 1928 (Flatfolder 52)
    - Palazzo Verza-Italian Renaissance columns, ink and watercolor on paper, [no date] (Flatfolder 52)
    - India Ink Rendering, [no date] (Flatfolder 52)
    - "Twenty-One"-rendering of a Gothic church, ink and watercolor on paper, 1927 (Flatfolder 52)
    - "Analytique," ink, black watercolor, and charcoal on paper, 1927 (Flatfolder 52)
    - Competition Entry, view of Aztec buildings, ink and watercolor on paper, 1932 (Flatfolder 53)
    - Interior of a combined library and chapel, ink and watercolor on paper, [no date] (Flatfolder 53)
    - D.H. Howe Prize, "Consolidated ticket office," ink and charcoal on paper, 1928 (Flatfolder 53)
    - Rendering of a building facade, pencil and charcoal on paper, 1933 (Flatfolder 53)
    - Rendering of a building facade, ink and charcoal on paper, 1933 (Flatfolder 53)
    - Plan of two story, two bedroom house, ink and pencil on paper, 1933 (Flatfolder 53)
    - Two story house, bedrooms omitted, ink, pencil, and charcoal on paper, 1933 (Flatfolder 53)
  - Music Pavilion and Outdoor Theatre at Grandview Park, Sioux City, Iowa, Working drawings, 12 sheets, ink on linen, 1934 (Flatfolder 54)
  - Competition Entries (Flatfolder 55)
    - Oregon State Capitol Competition, 8 sheets, ink on paper, [no date]
    - Art Center for Wheaton College, Norton, Massachusetts, 8 sheets, ink on paper, [no date]
    - Seventh Schermerhorn Fellowship, "A Small College for Men," 5 sheets, ink on paper, 1939
  - Proposed Shell for Murphy High School, Mobile, Alabama, Cross Section and Overhead View, #1, ink on linen, 1944 (Flatfolder 56)
  - Music Pavilion at Oleson Park, Fort Dodge, Iowa, Working drawings, 9 sheets, ink on linen, 1936
  - Johnson Addition, Norman, Oklahoma, Working drawings, pencil on tracing paper, 6 sheets, 1947 (Flatfolder 57)
  - J. Robert Landsaw Residence, Floor plan, first floor, basement; Elevation of kitchen cabinet and stair rail, 1944 (Flatfolder 57)
  - Kamphoefner Residence, Norman, Oklahoma
    - Sections of studio and bedroom, 1942 (Flatfolder 57)
    - Full scale drawings, pencil on tracing paper, 3 sheets, 1942 (Flatfolder 57)
    - Working Drawings, pencil on tracing paper, 11 sheets, 1942 (Flatfolder 57)
  - Edwards Mausoleum, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 7 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 57)
  - Wenger Band Wagon, Working Drawings, 10 sheets, pencil on tracing paper, [no date] (Flatfolder 57)
  - Oklahoma Solar House Project, Libby-Owens-Ford Glass Company (Flatfolder 58)
    - Memo, blueprints of the sun's position, 1947
    - Sun's azimuth angles, blueprint
    - Working drawings, blueprints, 20 sheets (2 sets)
  - Kamphoefner Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina (Flatfolder 59)
    - Design sketch of facade, pencil on tracing paper
    - Design sketch of floor plan, pencil on paper
    - Plot plan, blueprint
    - Plot plan, xerographic copy
    - Terrace addition, xerographic copy, [no date]
    - Landscape detail by Lewis Clarke, xerographic copy, 1961
    - Plot plan by Lewis Clarke, xerographic copy, [no date]
    - Landscape detail by Lewis Clarke, pencil and ink on tracing paper
    - Original working drawings, tracings, 13 sheets, drawn by George Matsumoto
  - McEvare Residence, Southern Pines, North Carolina, Blueprints and drawings (Flatfolder 60)
    - Drawing of McEvare residence, 1952
    - Plan of the Interior, excluding the breezeway, 1952
    - Plan for St. Charles kitchen for McEvare Residence, Town and Country, 1952
    - Topographic plan for McEvare plot, 1952
    - Exterior of McEvare residence detailing North and South elevations, 1952
    - Interior plan for McEvare residence, "Skyline,", 1952
    - Miscellaneous construction and design markups, 17 sheets, blueprints, 1952
    - McEvare Residence, Southern Pines, North Carolina, Working drawings, pencil and ink on tracing paper, 11 sheets, with specifications, 1952 (Flatfolder 61)
    - Proposed Residence for Mr. and Mrs. Rowland L. McEvare, "Skyline," Design drawings, pencil and ink on tracing paper, 8 sheets, 1952 (Flatfolder 61)
  - General Electric Demonstration House, ink and pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 61)
    - Preliminary Studies, detail sketch, 1952 (Flatfolder 62)
    - Preliminary Studies, north, south, east, west elevations, 1952 (Flatfolder 62)
    - Cross section A-A, B-B, 1952 (Flatfolder 62)
    - North, south, east, west elevation, 1952 (Flatfolder 62)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1932-1949 (Box 63)
    - 1936-1948 (Box 64)
    - 1948-1959 (Box 65)
    - 1957-1963 (Box 66)
    - 1952-1955 (Box 67)
    - 1948-1952 (Box 68)
    - 1952-1960 (Box 69)
    - 1955-1959 (Box 70)
    - 1959-1962 (Box 71)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 72)
    - 1965-1968 (Box 73)
    - 1968-1973 (Box 74)
  - Kamphoefner Portfolio, 1945 (Box 75)
- Project Specifications, 1932-1947
  - Pike Addition, Sioux City, Iowa, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Building, Sioux City, Iowa, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Crescent Jewelry Company, Sioux City, Iowa, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Grandview Music Pavilion, Sioux City, Iowa, 1934-1936 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Ft. Dodge Music Pavilion, Ft. Dodge, Iowa, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 10)